Guide to the Denise Levertov Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 11. Manuscripts by Others
  - Smith, Pauline. "Denise Levertov's poetry: the theme of celebration", 1972, TMs, 79 pp. (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Speirs, Heather. "The contemplative poems of Denise Levertov: an oblique path to the Creator", n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Speirs, Logan. "The New Poetry", n.d., TMs, 23 pp. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Stafford, Kim R. "Writing daily, writing in tune", n.d., TMs, 1 p. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Stegner Fellows: Catacalos, Rosemary, 1990 Winter (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Stegner Fellows: Cusac, Anne-Marie, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Stegner Fellows: Kelly-Dewitt, Susan, 1990 Winter (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Stegner Fellows: Kuhn, Jessica, 1990 Winter (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Stegner Fellows: Lunday, Robert, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Stegner Fellows: Manley, Curtis, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Stegner Fellows: Neelon, Ann, 1990 Winter (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Stegner Fellows: Saenz, Benjamin Alire, 1990 Winter (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Stegner Fellows: Schmidt, Larry, 1990 Winter (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Stegner Fellows: Towle, Andrew, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Stegner Fellows: Vasquez, Robert, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Stegner Fellows: misc., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Stein, Dona Luongo. "The fallen are rising", n.d. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Stein, Dona Luongo. Poems, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Stever, Margo. Poems, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Stowell, Phyllis. "A possible life", n.d., TMs, 2 pp. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Strasser, Arnold E. "To Denise Levertov", 1967, TMs, TLS (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Sullivan, William. "Denise Levertov Goodman", n.d., AMs (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Tarlo, Harriet. "Eye, breath, & song", 1990, TMs, 26 pp. + ALS (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "Things falling", n.d. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Thorpe, Douglas. "Bottom's dream: relfections on poetry and the contemplative": preface, chapter 3, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Thorpe, Douglas. "Landscape into heart, hand, & mind", n.d., TMs, 5 pp. (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Thorpe, Douglas. "Moving through transformation: introduction", n.d., TMs, 9 pp. + TLS (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Thorpe, Douglas. "Reading (for Denise Levertov, February 11, 1976)", 1976 Feb. 11, TMsS, 1 p. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - [Katz-Levine, Judy]. "To Denise and Ellen", n.d., TMs, 1 p. (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Tontonghi, Steve. "Ravenna Park Bridge (for Geoff)", n.d., TMs, 1 p. (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Tontonghi, Steve. Poems., n.d., TMs (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Treitel, Jonathan., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Treitel, Jonathan. "The bloody old hole", n.d. (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Triem, Eve. "The summing up (for Denise Levertov)", n.d., TMsS, 1 p. (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Trueblood, Valerie. "Evangel"; "Think not bitterly of me", n.d., TMs, 22 pp.; TMs, 35 pp. (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Trueblood, Valerie. "Notes on Hegel", n.d. (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Trueblood, Valerie. "Orogeny"; Phantom Father"; "The silkie", n.d., TMs, 6 pp.; TMs, 11 pp.; TMS, 40 pp. (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Ugolnik, Anton. "Unity and the Orthodox Sensibility", n.d. (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - [Unknown author]. "Friend of Mark's", 1991 Jan. 15 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Valdez, Luis. Commencement Address, Santa Clara University, 1992 June 13 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Van de Kamp, Alexandra., n.d., TMs, 4 pp. + ALS (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Wakoski, Diane. "Brief chart analysis and introduction to astrology, for Denise Levertov", n.d., TMs, with holographic notes, 10 pp.; AMs, 9 pp.; ALS (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Walker, Jeanne Murray. "The question od idolatry: saving images in Denise Levertov's poetry", 1995 Mar. 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Wallach, Joelle. "Toward a time of renewal: for chorus, orchestra, and solo voices" [sheet music], 1993, based on texts by Denise Levertov (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Wallace, Jan. Poems, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Wallace, Janet L. "Hand/Heart": draft, 1995 June, TMs (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Wallace, Janet L. "Hand/Heart", n.d., TMs (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - [Warn], Emily. Poems, 1997 Dec. 6, TMs, 4 pp. + TLS (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Warn, Emily. Poems, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Wasserburg, Chuck. "The blue bicycle", n.d., TMs, 1 p. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Watsky, Joshua. Translations of Guillevic, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Weatherly, Thomas E.J. "2 women, a child", 1967 May 10, TMsS (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Wendt, Ingrid. "Questions of Grace", n.d., TMs, TLS from John Haines (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - West, Bronson. Poems, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Whilan, Susan., 1997, TMs, 7 pp. + TLS (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Whitney, J.D. "The children of Nicaragua", 1984 Nov., TMs, with holographic notes, 1 p. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Wilder, Amos N. "An old family argument", n.d., TMs (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Winters, Yvor. "To Herman Melville in 1951", n.d., TMs, 1 p. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Wenborn, Neil., n.d. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Wolkstein, Diane. "Dream songs: Abulafia, part of my heart", n.d., includes AMs review by Denise Levertov (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Woodhams, Wilbur Charles. "Meditation on Christmas", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - [Wright, James Arlington. Collected Poems. Middleton, CT: Wesleyan Univ. Press]: galley proofs, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Wright, Charles. "Signature", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Wright, Ralph., 1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Writing woman interview with Denise Levertov, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - "You and I (for Denise)", n.d., TMsS, 1 p. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Young, Al. "Moon Poems": selections, n.d., TMs (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Zaslawsky, Cheryl. "Prayer", 1993 Feb. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Zaslawsky, Cheryl. "Seeing your aura", n.d., TMs, 1 p. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Zlotkowski, Edward. "The little green frog", n.d., TMs, 9 pp. (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Zlotkowski, Edward. "Planning for the future (for Denise)", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Zlotkowski, Edward. "The poet's religion: Levertov and Christianity", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Zlotkowski, Edward. "The sky tree", n.d., TMs, 8 pp. (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Zlotkowski, Edward., n.d. (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Zscheile, Dwight. "Journal of Ash", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Zscheile, Dwight. "Windshock", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - unidentified manuscripts, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - unidentified manuscripts and fragments, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - unidentified manuscripts and fragments, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - unidentified manuscripts and fragments, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Series 12. Artifacts
  - Lath box lid, painted, initialed "DL", 1941, includes 4 pieces of lace, 1 baby's slipper, 2 baby's hood (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Note with two stones, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Envelope with feathers and dried flowers, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Postcard collection, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rev. Paul Philip Levertoff Doctor of Divinity diploma and seal, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 1)